Guide to the Mary Dowdell Ashley Film Collection, 1937-1975 RL.10048
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Films, 1936-1967; 1
  - Reel 17, 1950; 13
    Additional description: Reel 13. Sequence 69. Scene 1. Mary Esther, FL (cont'd); Pier & boat (possibly Uncle Phil's), probably in front of Aunt Mamie & Uncle Phil's house: Bill? Thetford in mostly blue shirt; Ginny in plaid shirt; Mother in blue checked shirt & male leaning on boat; Bill? Thetford dove & Ginny jumped off pier & swam; both get on pier; on beach, Mother & Bonnie (baby); close-up of Ann & then Bonnie with almost no hair on left side of head (note: Bonnie went through stage of pulling out her hair on left side, probably when taking naps -- eventually overcame this practice); Bonnie playing in sand & in shallow water; Daddy sitting on edge of small boat; Bonnie & Ann standing in blue bathing suits; view of Santa Rosa Sound, pier & house -- Ann & Bonnie sitting on steps. 13* on original list, but contents of reel 13 are on reel 12.
    - Original 16mm film, 1950; 150 film feet (Box 1, Film-reel RL10048-F16-0013)